♪ Hey ♪
♪ Uh-huh-huh ♪
♪ What I like about
you you hold me tight ♪
♪ Tell me I'm the only one ♪
♪ Wanna come over tonight yeah ♪
♪ Keep on whispering in my ear ♪
♪ Tell me all the things
that I wanna hear ♪
♪ 'Cause it's true ♪
♪ That's what I like about you ♪
♪ What I like about you you
really know how to dance ♪
♪ When you go up down jump around ♪
♪ Think about true romance yeah ♪
♪ Keep on whispering in my ear ♪
♪ Tell me all the things
that I wanna hear ♪
♪ 'Cause it's true ♪
♪ That's what I like about you ♪
♪ Woo ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ What I like about you
you keep me warm at night ♪
♪ Never wanna let you go know
you make me feel alright yeah ♪
♪ Keep on whispering in my ear ♪
♪ Tell me all the things
that I wanna hear ♪
♪ 'Cause it's true ♪
♪ That's what I like about you ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Uh-huh-huh ♪
♪ Hey hey hey ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Uh-huh-huh brr ♪
♪ Uh-huh-huh ♪
♪ Hey ♪